<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Valerie Langlois</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Valerie Langlois</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualtrics Data Management</title>
      <link>/blog/qualtrics-data-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/qualtrics-data-management/</guid>
      <description>This is for output from Qualtrics that is downloaded in non-legacy format (for scoring on the Author Recognition Task). Before running Before running the Qualtrics survey, make sure to name all your stimuli and corresponding questions so that they are distinguishable from other questions (i.e. consent, age, gender, etc.). If I have an item with two follow up questions, I name them as such:
 S01_Q1: Where S01 is the item number (or T01), and Q1 is the first question</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Qualtrics Data Management</title>
      <link>/post/qualtrics-data-management/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/qualtrics-data-management/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Website</title>
      <link>/blog/new-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/new-website/</guid>
      <description>After many hours of googling and trial and error, I finally succeeded in creating an academic website to replace my old Wordpress one from UNC. I probably spent more time than I should have on this “small” project, but I think the struggle was worth it.
There’s a whole website detailing how to create a website using Blogdown in R (and R Markdown). I think most of my troubles came from the fact that I used a different theme than the one from their example, since some themes are not compatible with Blogdown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m a graduate student in the Cognitive Psychology program at University of North Carolina Chapel Hill, working with Dr. Jennifer Arnold. I graduated from University of Rochester in 2016 with a B.S. in Brain &amp;amp; Cognitive Science and a B.A. in Linguistics.
I am currently interested in how distributional information in language affects the informativity of different communicative signals. My hope is that somewhere along my grad school journey, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to incorporate my interests in machine learning with my interests in language learning 😄 UNC Chapel Hill:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>/pubs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/pubs/</guid>
      <description>Fraundorf, S. H., Arnold, J. E., Langlois, V.J. (2018) “Disfluency.” In Oxford Bibliographies in Linguistics. Ed. Mark Aronoff. New York: Oxford University Press. Link. — Published in 2014, updated in 2018
Talks:
Langlois, V. J., Arnold, J. E. (2019) Individual differences guide pronoun interpretation in semantically constraining contexts. Departmental talk given at the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill
Langlois, V. J., Zerkle, S. A., Arnold, J. E. (2018) Does planning explain predictability effects on word duration?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>